all okay okay guys we have with us Mr
Shan we'll take one question at time who
want to work first yes please
uh but I
think
[Laughter]
um Shan congrats uh you read the final
in your first World Cup uh tournament
you've done well of course you won the
junior World Cup as well uh um how does
it feel and also when they were chasing
they were doing fairly well at one part
of time limson and um Mitchell how did
you how did the team deal with that
honestly I think we knew it was going to
be challenging uh especially under the
lights on this once the new ball gets a
bit old it is a bit difficult for
bowlers here to you know contain run so
we knew it's going to be challenging but
what was important for us was to just
keep bowling the areas where we wanted
to ball and wait for them to make a
mistake and that's what we did and I
think darl land at one point darlan Kan
the partnership that they had it was
looking a bit challenging but with such
big scores you know you know couple of
fets here and there you're always in the
game your own your own um performance
reaching the final having won the junior
World Cup as feels great you know I'm in
the way our batting balling and fiing
the way we have dominated in this world
cup it's just as a player to be able to
play with all all those players uh
sitting in the dressing it's just been a
magnificent run for
us can you talk about M shab
[Music]
successful
what kind of exchanges you have in the
middle uh honestly
because
[Music]
think single double single double
because I think we compliment our game
quite well so I think it works quite
well in the
middle
what about opening with Rohit you know
what have you learned from him and how I
mean is there something which really
impresses you about the partnership all
everything you know everything about him
really impresses me
[Music]
and here this team has conquered
everything they have won everything and
it seems like they're Invincible in this
world cup what is it that this makes
this team this apart from the skill set
whether it's the atmosphere is there
something that brings the together as a
group what is it from your point of view
I think one that we've been this this
team I think have been we've been
playing together for like the past one
year or so and I think we know our roles
quite well and I think the difference
that has been for me personally honestly
it's been our bowling attack the way our
bowling attack has bowled uh they have
in I think in all the matches they've
always uh either defended the total or
restricted the other team to a blow par
score so I think that's been the
difference Shan just extending that
question regarding your role when you're
opening with Rohit how difficult does it
get to kind of hold that Temptation back
because he's going all out from one end
so what is your role during that period
because we saw after he got out you kind
of started playing your shots more
freely so is that the plan that you know
as long as he there you'll be kind of
seeing it through and then go big after
he goes honestly when he was there I
didn't get that many balls
so after that I started to get no I mean
honestly my role is just you know play
my game in the power play uh look for
good shots look for good boundaries and
then once the power play is over because
I rotate the strike quite well then you
know rotate the uh rotate to the
Spinners and then once you are in then
it's all about you and your instinct how
you how you play how you you know see
which bowler to take on if the bowler is
under a bit of pressure then you know
when to take on it's all about reading
the game after
that shman I assume you grew up watching
verat play all the time and you battered
with him today on the day he scored his
50th Century I just wondered what that
was like for
you you know every time he comes on to
the park he does something special and
uh just how consistently he's been able
to do it for the past 10 15 years is
what is really uh
inspiring and I think it's for me it's
not so much about the skill that he has
but it's more about the hunger when he
goes there and the intensity at which he
plays the game is what inspires me and
to be able to have that consistently for
a for as long as he's he's been doing it
is what really inspires me can I just
ask your injury are you okay what
happened there it it started with cramps
and then uh I pulled my hamstring a
little bit and I think these are just
the it was quite humid and just the
after effects of for dingo you think
you'll be okay for Sunday yeah
definitely question shman you've got a
100% record in World Cup finals um with
the mount Mangan who we beenn in Tanga
um you're going back to your home ground
which is for the Gujarat Titans you're
playing in front of 130,000 people
potentially um this journey has been
fantastic over the last four years
you're the only one from that batch
which has kind of made that transition
into the team currently how does it all
feel how do you take it in and how do
you keep yourself
grounded honestly there are like lot of
things to look forward to right now we
have the finals after that we'd have
some other important series but uh those
are all in hindsight right now and if
you are always looking for something uh
to look forward to then it it it keeps
you grounded cuz there's something for
you to always work
on question shman you mentioned your
Deni just now and having recovered from
that uh physically like over all these
games that you've played like how
difficult has it been and has have you
had to like adjust something in how you
bat or anything about your game at all
not really I honestly not really
adjusted anything in terms of my batting
but because I've lost a bit of uh muscle
mass I think the reserve that I used to
have before the dingo has decreased a
little bit and that's why generally I
don't really get cramps when uh like you
do get cramps when you're playing in
humid conditions but that happens for me
it happens after a long period of time
not not uh so soon but because I think
I've lost a bit of muscle mass the
reserve has gone down a bit thank you
thank you